https://www.hazmatinc.com/privacypolicy

privacy-Policy — HazMat Environmental Group, Inc.
PRIVACY POLICY
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices and policies for Hazmat Environmental Group, Inc.. We respect our customers and understand that you are concerned about privacy, so we've instituted policies intended to ensure that your personal information is handled safely and responsibly. We also have posted this privacy policy to let you know what kind of information we collect, how it is handled, with whom it may be shared, and what choices you have regarding our use of your information. If you have any questions about this policy, you can contact us by telephone at 716.827.7200.
What Information Do We Collect?
We collect your name and email address.
Do We Share Your Information?
The information gathered may be shared with corporate affiliates of Hazmat Environmental Group, Inc.. We may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law or to protect our interests or property. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, credit bureaus, agents or government agencies in connection with issues related to fraud, credit or debt collection. Finally, in the event that some or all of our business assets are sold or transferred, we generally would transfer the corresponding information about our customers.
Additional Privacy Information In addition to the privacy information contained herein, you may be entitled to additional privacy protections by state and federal law.
Please use the "Contact Us" link or call us at (716) 827-7200 for more information. Quick LinksHomeTransportationEquipmentSafety and SecurityTraining and ConsultingRepairsEmploymentResource LibraryContact Us
© 2018 Hazmat Environmental Group, Inc. All rights reserved. Privacy Policy
Back To Top
HazMat Environmental Group, Inc., 60 Commerce Drive, Buffalo, NY, 14218, United States(716) 827-7200
